Guide to the Irving McNeil Ives papers, 1862-1958
Ives, Irving McNeil papers, 1862-1958
- SERIES I. CORRESPONDENCE and LEGISLATION
  - State Assembly Correspondence: K-M - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 22)
    highway (legislation), education
  - State Assembly Correspondence: N-P - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 23)
    education (state aid)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: Q-S - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 24)
    education, taxation
  - State Assembly Correspondence: T-Z - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 25)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: 3/33 - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 26)
    tax protests, taxation
  - State Assembly Correspondence: 3/33-4/33 - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 27)
    taxation
  - State Assembly Postcards: 2/33-3/33 - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 28)
    protest tax increase; taxation
  - State Assembly Correspondence: 2/33, 3/33, 4/33 - 1933 (Box 169, Folder 29)
    public opinion telegrams: taxation, wages, health care
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-B - 1934 (Box 169, Folder 30)
    education (state aid), taxation
  - State Assembly Correspondence: C-D - 1934 (Box 169, Folder 31)
    taxation, education
  - State Assembly Correspondence: E-F - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: G-H - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    education (state aid), education (teacher's oath)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: I-J-K - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    education (state Aid), taxation
  - State Assembly Correspondence: L-M - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    education (state Aid), osteopathy (regulations)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: N-O - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: P-R - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    education (legislation), utilities (regulation)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: S - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: T-U-V - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    education (teacher's oath), education (legislation), utilities (legislation)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: W-Z - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    education (legislation)
  - State Assembly Correspondence - 1934 (Box 173, Folder 9A)
    telegrams
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    election (1935 campaign)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: B - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    election (1935 campaign), Republican Party program (1936 legislation)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: C-D - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: E-F-G - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    election (1935 campaign), patronage
  - State Assembly Correspondence: H-I-J - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 14)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: K-L - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 15)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M-N - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 16)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: O-P-Q-R - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 17)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: S-T - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 18)
  - State Assembly Correspondence:U-Z - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 19)
    New York Assembly (organization)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: no name - 1935 (Box 173, Folder 20)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-C - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 21)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: D-F - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 22)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: letters to Melvin C. Eaton - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 23)
    agriculture; Frank Gannett
  - State Assembly Correspondence: G-H - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 24)
    patronage; Frank Gannett, Albert Haskell, Jr.
  - State Assembly Correspondence: I-L - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 25)
    anti-crime legislation, taxation, patronage
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 26)
    Republican Party politics (N. Y. S.), election (1936 campaign); Walter J. Mahoney
  - State Assembly Correspondence: N-P - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 27)
    labor laws (equality for women), N. Y. S. Assembly (organization); Harold Ostertag
  - State Assembly Correspondence: Q-S - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 28)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: T-Z - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 29)
    election (1936 campaign), N. Y. S. Assembly (organization); Pliny W. Williamson
  - State Assembly Correspondence: no name - 1936 (Box 173, Folder 30)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-B - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 31)
    patronage; Dean Alfange
  - State Assembly Correspondence: C-D - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 32)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: E-G - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 33)
    patronage, Melvin Eaton
  - State Assembly Correspondence: H-K - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 34)
    N.Y.S. Assembly; Oswald Heck
  - State Assembly Correspondence: L - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 35)
    Constitutional Convention, wage and hour (legislation); Herbert A. Lehman, Bert Lord
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M-N - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 36)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: O-R - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 37)
    interstate cooperation, patronage; Harold Ostertag
  - State Assembly Correspondence: S-T - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 38)
    Republican Party (N.Y.S.); Stanley Shaw, Jane Todd
  - State Assembly Correspondence: U-Z - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 39)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: no name - telegrams - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 41)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A - 1938 (Box 173, Folder 42)
    social welfare, patronage; David C. Adie
  - State Assembly Correspondence: B - 1938 (Box 173, Folder 43)
    labor relations, patronage, industry (legislation); Bindell Bixby
  - State Assembly Correspondence: C - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    patronage, Marion M. Crain
  - State Assembly Correspondence: D-E - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    patronage, Melvin C. Eaton
  - State Assembly Correspondence: F-G - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    patronage; Ralph Gamble, Frank Gannett, Mark Graves
  - State Assembly Correspondence: H-I-J - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: K-L - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    patronage; Bert Lord
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: N-O - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    patronage, interstate cooperation (N. Y. S. Assembly Comm.)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: P-R - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    Dutton S. Peterson
  - State Assembly Correspondence: S - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    S: patronage; Stanley C. Shaw
  - State Assembly Correspondence: T-U-V - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    profit sharing (legislation), Republican Party; Jane Todd, Arthur H. Vandenberg
  - State Assembly Correspondence: W-Z - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: no name - 1938 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-C - 1939 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    social welfare (legislation); David C. Adie
  - State Assembly Correspondence: D-H - 1939 (Box 174, Folder 14)
    patronage; Thomas E. Dewey
  - State Assembly Correspondence: I-L - 1939 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    education (state aid); Herbert Lehman
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M-P - 1939 (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: Q-Z - 1939 (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-C - 1940 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: D-G - 1940 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: H-L - 1940 (Box 174, Folder 20)
    patronage, Oswald C. Heck
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M-P - 1940 (Box 174, Folder 21)
    Rural Rehabilitation Corp., presidential election (1940 campaign)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: R-Z - 1940 (Box 174, Folder 22)
    Wendell L. Willkie
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-C - 1940 (Box 174, Folder 23)
    patronage, John E. Burton
  - State Assembly Correspondence: D-F - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 24)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: G-H - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 25)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: J-L - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 26)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 27)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: O-R - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 28)
    interstate co-operation, patronage, closed shop; Harold Ostertag
  - State Assembly Correspondence: S-T - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 29)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: U-Z - 1941 (Box 174, Folder 30)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-F - 1942 (Box 174, Folder 31)
    patronage, Division of Commerce (N. Y. S.); M. P. Catherwood
  - State Assembly Correspondence: - 1942 (Box 174, Folder 32)
    patronage, taxes; Oswald D. Heck
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M-R - 1942 (Box 174, Folder 33)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: S-Z - 1942 (Box 174, Folder 34)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-G - 1943 (Box 174, Folder 35)
    labor legislation (Columbia University), real property (assessments)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: H-M - 1943 (Box 174, Folder 36)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: N-S - 1943 (Box 174, Folder 37)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: T-Z - 1943 (Box 174, Folder 38)
    patronage, Wendell L. Willkie
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-C - 1944 (Box 174, Folder 39)
    legislative experiment; American Legion, Phillips Bradley
  - State Assembly Correspondence: D-K - 1944 (Box 174, Folder 40)
    speaking engagements, politics; Albert Haskell, Jr.
  - State Assembly Correspondence: M-N - 1944 (Box 174, Folder 41)
    politics; New York Civic League; O. R. Miller
  - State Assembly Correspondence: P-Z - 1944 (Box 174, Folder 42)
    politics
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-H - 1945 (Box 174, Folder 43)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: I-P - 1945 (Box 174, Folder 44)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: Q-Z - 1945 (Box 174, Folder 45)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: A-D - 1946 (Box 174, Folder 46)
    education (teachers salaries)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: E-J - 1946 (Box 174, Folder 47)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: K-O - 1946 (Box 174, Folder 48)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: P-Z - 1946 (Box 174, Folder 49)
  - State Assembly Correspondence: no name - 1946 (Box 174, Folder 50)
  - State Assembly Correspondence - 1946 (Box 174, Folder 51)
  - State Assembly Correspondence - 19--, [1930-1946] (Box 174, Folder 52)
  - State Assembly Information booklets re Legislature of State of New York (pamphlets) - 1927-1928, 1933-1934, 1936, 1938-1940, 1943 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    Rules of the Assembly - 1938, 1939, 1941, 1942; The Clerks Manual - 1936, 1938, 1940, 1941, 1943; Members, Officers and Standing Committee - 1927-1928, 1940, 1943; Comm. Directory of Assembly 1933-1934, 1940
  - N. Y. S. Assembly Jr. Legislative Comm. To Study Progress and Suppression of Bovine Tuberculosis in N. Y. S. - [1931] (Box 175, Folder 2)
    bovine tuberculosis
  - State Assembly Farm Records and Bank Statements - 1931-1932 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - State Assembly Misc. Assembly - Taxation Sales, Gasoline, etc. - 1932-1934 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - State Assembly Misc. Assembly material - 1932-1933 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    lobbying (N. Y. S. Hairdressers and Cosmetologists Assoc.); New York City (legislative investigation)
  - State Assembly Assembly Bank Comm. - 1934 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    Credit Union Movement; N. Y. S. Credit Union League
  - State Assembly Billage Education Correspondence - 1934 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - State Assembly Education Comm. - Correspondence - 1934 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    education (legislation), drug products (legislation)
  - State Assembly Child Labor Amendment - 1934 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    U. S. Constitution (Child Labor Amendment)
  - State Assembly Misc. - 1934 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    Publicity, Personal injuries
  - State Assembly Misc. Material ?Analysis of Bills introduced - 1935 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    N. Y. S. Assembly (legislation)
  - N. Y. S. Assembly ?(Organization) - 1935 (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - State Assembly I.M.I. as Minority Leader - 1935 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    N. Y. S. Legislature (minority leader); Albert Haskell
  - Budget material N. Y. S. Legislature - [1936] (Box 175, Folder 14-15)
    Appropriations (N. Y. S.)
  - State Assembly Legislative Utility Investigation - 1929, 1933, 1935 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    utilities, N. Y. S. (investigation)
  - State Assembly Misc. - 1935 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    reapportionment, crime (conference), salaries (Sing Sing guards); Herbert H. Lehman
  - State Assembly Confidential - Mr. Washburn - 1935 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    N. Y. S. Legislature (Assembly speaker)
  - State Assembly - Lehman, Hon. Herbert H. - 1935-1936, 1939 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    N. Y. S. Legislature (Routine Business)
  - State Assembly - I.M.I. as speaker - 1936 (Box 175, Folder 20)
    Speaker, N. Y. S. Assembly
  - State Assembly - Anti-Crime Program - Legislature - 1936 (Box 175, Folder 21)
    anti-crime program (N. Y. S.); Herbert H. Lehman
  - State Assembly - Flood Control - 1936 (Box 175, Folder 22)
  - State Assembly - Ways and Means - State Budget - 1936 (Box 175, Folder 23)
    state budget (N.Y.S.)
  - State Assembly - State Department of Social Welfare - Reorganization - 1936 (Box 175, Folder 24)
    Department of Social Welfare (N. Y. S.)
  - State Assembly - Social Security Program - 1936 (Box 175, Folder 25)
  - State Assembly Taxation data - 1936-1937 (Box 175, Folder 26)
    taxation (N. Y. S.)
  - State Assembly Material - 1936 (Box 175, Folder 27)
    education, child labor (legislation), public welfare
  - State Fiscal Policies, Assembly Legislation Comm. - 1937 (Box 175, Folder 28-29)
    fiscal policies, N. Y. S.; State of New York; Joint Legislative Committee on State Fiscal Policies
  - State Assembly Material - Re: organization Assembly Legislative Hearing on Minimum Wage, milk controls, Federal Control of Youth Amendment - 1937 (Box 175, Folder 30)
    Assembly, N. Y. S. (organization), wages, milk controls
  - State Assembly Legislature - Misc. material - 1937 (Box 175, Folder 31)
    Hon. Elihu Root
  - State Assembly - Extraordinary Session - 1937 (Box 175, Folder 32)
    Administrative Code (NYC)
  - State Assembly - Organization - 1938 (Box 175, Folder 33)
    legislation (N. Y. S.)
  - State Assembly Legislature - Labor Program - 1937-1938 (Box 175, Folder 34)
    labor (legislation); Comm. For Industrial Organization, N. Y. S. Federation of Labor
  - N. Y. S. Legislative Comm. on Interstate Cooperation - Preliminary Report on Interstate Cooperation in Liquor Regulation - 1938 (Box 175, Folder 35)
    Liquor regulations, interstate cooperation
  - State Assembly Press Releases - Bills signed by Gov. - Bills returned by Gov - 1938 (Box 175, Folder 36)
  - N. Y. S. Constitutional Convention Committee - 1937-1938 (Box 175, Folder 37)
    constitution (N. Y. S.); Herbert H. Lehman
  - N. Y. S. Constitutional Convention Committee - 1915, 1938 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    constitution (N. Y. S.)
  - N. Y. S. Constitutional Convention - 1938 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Assembly Material - 1938 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - N. Y. S. Legislature - Budget and Taxation - [1939] (Box 176, Folder 4)
    budget (N. Y. S.), taxation (N. Y. S.)
  - Legislature - The Budget - 1939 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    budget (N. Y. S.)
  - Legislature - Extraordinary Session - 1939 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    judge (removal)
  - State Assembly Hearing on Executive Budget - 1940 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - State Assembly Material - 1940 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    organization, national defense, education - state aid to
  - State Assembly Highway Programs - 1940 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    highway (legislation), highways (funding); N. Y. S. Construction Council
  - State Assembly Legislative material - 1941 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    dairy industry (Bang's disease control), real estate, national defense; N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Committee on Interstate Cooperation
  - State Assembly Report - Joint Legislative Committee on Assessing and Reviewing of the State of New York - 1941 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - State Assembly Report - Joint Legislative Committee to Investigate Procedures and methods of allocating state monies for public school purposes and subversive activities - 1941 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    education (financing), subversive activities
  - State Assembly Burton, John E. - 1941 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    labor (legislative research); John E. Burton
  - State Assembly - 1942 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    post war planning (employment), post planning (public works), education (state aid), reforestation (N. Y. S.)
  - State Assembly Health Insurance Plan for State of New York 12/11/42 - 1942 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - State Assembly - 1943 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    Assembly, N. Y. S. (organization), labor program, Democratic Party Program (1943)
  - State Assembly Reports - Joint Legislative Comm. on Interstate Cooperation - 1942-1943 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    interstate cooperation; New York Joint Legislative Comm. on Interstate Cooperation
  - State Assembly Material - Misc. Reports - 1943 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    banking, labor relations
  - State of New York Assembly. Temporary Economy Commission. Reports - 1943 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    economy (N.Y.S.)
  - State Assembly N. Y. S. Conference Bd. of Farm Organizations, 1944 - Citizen's Conference 1943 - Skaneateles, etc - 1943-1944 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    agriculture (legislative program), post-war planning
  - State Assembly N. Y. S. Citizens Council for a Durable peace - conference - 1943-1944 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    peace (Citizens Conference); N. Y. S. Citizen's Council for a Durable Peace
  - State Assembly material - Election laws - 1943 (Box 176, Folder 22)
    election laws, reapportionment
  - State Assembly 1943 Chenango County - Public Health - 1943 (Box 176, Folder 23)
    public health
  - State Assembly Material - 1944 (Box 176, Folder 24)
    N. Y. S. Assembly (committees and temporary commissions), budget message (Governor); laws (N. Y. S.)
  - State Assembly Veterans Service Centers - [1944] (Box 176, Folder 25)
    veterans affairs
  - State Assembly Report - Joint Legislative Committee to Inquire into and study Legislative Methods, practices, procedures and expenditures - 1945 (Box 176, Folder 26)
    legislative inquiry; N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Committee to Inquire into and Study Legislative methods
  - State Assembly Material Misc. reports and correspondence - 1945 (Box 176, Folder 27)
    labor law; experience rating; Carpshenks, Orangeburg, N. Y. (investigation); agriculture (education)
  - State Assembly Commission on Agriculture - 1945 (Box 176, Folder 28)
    agriculture (study of, N. Y. S.)
  - State Assembly Material - 1946 (Box 176, Folder 29)
    veterans benefits
  - State Assembly Misc. Material (undated) - 19-- (Box 176, Folder 30)
  - State Assembly Gov. Lehman - State of the State Messages - 1934-1942 (Box 176, Folder 31)
    N. Y. S. (proposed legislative directions); Herbert H. Lehman
  - Origin of Committee: State Assembly, Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial & Labor Conditions (JLCILC) - 19-- (Box 177, Folder 1)
    industrial and labor relations
  - JLCILC - Correspondence 6/38-7/38 - 1938 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    State of New York - JLCILC
  - JLCILC - Correspondence 8/38-9/38 - 1938 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    labor relations (N. Y. S. study)
  - JLCILC - Correspondence 10/38 - 1938 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    labor relations (N. Y. S. Study)
  - JLCILC - Correspondence 11/38 - 1938 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - JLCILC - Correspondence 12/38 - 1938, 1939 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial & Labor Relations (JLCILR) - Correspondence - 1938, 1940, 1944, 1946 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - New York State JLCILR - 1939 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    questionnaires
  - JLCILR - 1941 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    labor Relations; Donald M. Nelson, Rev. William J. Kelley O. M. I.
  - Labor Relations Comm. - (I.M.I.-Chr.) - 1938 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    labor Relations
  - N. Y. S. JLCILR - Bills - 1940 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    labor (legislation)
  - Proposed Labor Legislation by Committee - 1941-1942 (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Resolution (Labor Comm.) - [1942] (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - 11-29 - Hearing - 1938 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    labor relations, labor relations (Great Britain)
  - Labor, etc. Meeting 7/30/40 - 1940 (Box 177, Folder 15)
    labor relations
  - Meeting - Coordinating Committee Chr. 12/10/40 - 1940 (Box 177, Folder 16)
  - Labor re Exodus Moffat vs. Lehman - 1940 (Box 177, Folder 17)
  - Business Exodus - 1941-1942 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    business (exodus, N. Y. S.)
  - Meeting - Executive Comm. and Coordinating Committee 1/30/41 - 1941 (Box 177, Folder 19)
  - Joint Meeting (Minutes) 9/10/43. Interstate Co-op and Labor Comm. - 1943 (Box 177, Folder 20)
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - meeting 6/13/45 - 1945 (Box 177, Folder 21)
    small business
  - Meetings and Misc. - n.d. - 19-- (Box 177, Folder 22)
  - Labor - Father Kelley's Reports, etc. - 1940 (Box 177, Folder 23)
  - Father Kelley's Reports - 1941-42 (Box 177, Folder 24)
    industrial and labor conditions; William M. Kelley, O. M. I.
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Relations - 1938, 1939, 1943 (Box 177, Folder 25)
  - Memorandum on the Benjamin Report requested by the JLCILC - 1942 (Box 177, Folder 26)
    Labor Relations Board (N. Y. S.)
  - JLCILR. Experience rating in unemployment insurance compens. Bar Assoc. NYC 12/3/41 - 1941 (Box 177, Folder 27)
    experience ratings
  - JCLILR. Dinner Meeting on Post-war planning 12/3/41 - 1937-1938 (Box 177, Folder 28)
    post war planning (World War II)
  - JCLILC - Cross-picketing Bar Association NYC 12/5/41 - 1941 (Box 177, Folder 29)
  - JLCILC - 1942 (Box 177, Folder 30)
    Luncheon Meeting on post war planning 6/24/42: post war planning (World War II)
  - Joint Production Committees in England - [1943] (Box 177, Folder 31)
    labor conditions (England)
  - Report - Luel F. Johnson - 1944 (Box 177, Folder 32)
    industrial and labor conditions
  - Report - Joint Legislative Comm. to Investigate the Self-Regulation of Industry - 19-- (Box 177, Folder 33)
    industry
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Relations. Report - 19-- (Box 177, Folder 34)
  - 3 original copies - Preliminary Reports - Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Relations - 1939-1940 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Draft - 1940 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - State of New York - Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Committee on I.& L. R. - Legislative Doc. (1940) No. 57 - (Albany: J. B. Lyn Com., 1940) 77 pgs - 1940 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - State of New York. Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Comm. on I. & L. R. Legislative Doc. (1941). No. 51. (Albany: Fort Orange Press, 1941). 88 p - 1941 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Comm. on I. & L. R - 1942 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - 1943 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - 1944 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - 1945 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - 1946 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Report of the N. Y. S. Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - Information Bulletin #2, 9/46 - 1946 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    health, medical care
  - reprints - 19-- (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - Correspondence - 1940 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    labor relations (New York State Study)
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - Correspondence - 1941 (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - Correspondence - 1942 (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - Correspondence - 1943-1945 (Box 178, Folder 15)
  - N. Y. S. Comm. on I. & L. R. - Forums - 1941 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    labor forum
  - Labor Bills - Misc. reports - news articles - 1935, 1944 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Joint Legislative Comm. on Industrial and Labor Conditions - misc. reports to the committee - 1938, 19-- (Box 179, Folder 3)
    industrial and labor relations (investigation)